Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory5 Mss.B.B61.inventory05
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents G
  - Gordon, George Bryon (Box 32-33)
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1911 May 9
    - To Boas, 1911 May 30
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 22
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1914 May 15
    - To Boas, 1914 Sept. 30
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 21
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 June 1
    - To Boas, 1917 June 8
    - To Boas, 1917 June 9
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - See Also McHugh, J.M., May 9, 1919; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 24; 1p.
  - Gordon, H.P. (Box 33)
    - To Smith, 1909 Feb. 18
  - Gordon, Paul W. (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1933 July 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - (Enc: Copy of telegram dated 9-18-33 from Collett Copy of letter dated 9-2-33 to Gordon, Paul W. from Burrows, Elizabeth S.), 1933 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - (Enc: Copy of telegram Carter, Arletta to Gordon, Paul W. dated 9-30-33), 1933 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - (Enc: Copy of letter from West, Phebe to Gordon, Paul W., dated 9-4-33)
    - P.W. Gordon -- to Silva Beyer, 1933 June 23; 1p.
    - P.W. Gordon -- from Elizabeth S. Burrows, 1933 Sept. 2; 2p.
    - (Attached to letter from Gordon, Paul W. to Boas, F., dated 9-30-33)
    - P.W. Gordon -- from Arletta Carter, 1933 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - (Attached to letter from Gordon, Paul W. to Boas, F., dated Oct. 2, 1933)
    - P.W. Gordon -- from Phebe West, 1933 Sept. 4; 1p.
    - (Attached to letter from Gordon, Paul W. to Boas, F., dated Oct. 4, 1933)
  - Gordon, Sylvia (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 28; 1p.
      (Enc: Whitman, George. History of the United Student Peqce Committee)
  - Gordon, V. (Box 33)
    - To Boas, 1916 June 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 9
  - Gorion, E. bin (Box 33)
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 26; 1p.
  - Goris, J.A. (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Jan. 27; 1p.
  - Gortner, R.A. (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - R.A. Gortner -- to F.W.J. Heuser, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - R.A. Gortner -- to F.W.J. Heuser, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p.
  - Got, F. (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb.
  - Gottheil, Richard (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 26; 1p.
    - R. Gottheil -- to Catell, 1896 May 22
  - Gotthelf, Philip (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 9; 1p.
  - Gottschall, Morton (Box 33)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spein. Replies., Jan. 1938
  - Goubaud, C. Antonio (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - Goudreich, E. (Box 33)
    - To Boas, 1907 June 6; (postcard)
  - Gouin, L. (Box 33)
    - L. Gouin -- to C.M. Barbeau, 1918 Sept. 4; 1p.
  - Gouja Plasano P. (?) (Box 33)
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 19; 1p.
  - Gould, Joseph F. (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 See Dec. 31; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1920 See Dec. 31; 4p.
  - Gould, Marion K. (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept. 28
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 7
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1916 July 21
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1917 May 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 29; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 30; 4p.
  - Gow, J. Steele (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 23; 1p.
  - Gower, Levison (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p.
  - Gozzo, S.C. (Box 33)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 3; 2p.
  - Graduate Faculty of Political and Social Sciences
    See Lederer, E.
    See New School for Social Research
  - Graebner, F. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 July 1; (postcard)
    - To Boas, 1913 June 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Sept. 25
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 4; 4p.
  - Graebner, Paula (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 7; 2p.
  - Graffenried, Elwyn de (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 13; 1p.
  - Graham, David C. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1939 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 16; 2p.
  - Graham, Frank P. (Box 34)
    - See Boas, F. to Carlson, A.J. (From Boas), July 31, 1941
    - To Boas
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies. Jan. 1938, 1939 July 4; (telegram)
    - F.P. Graham -- to N.H. Dearborn, 1941 Aug. 11; 1p.
  - Graham, W.P. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 13; 1p.
  - Gramercy Braid & Trimming Co. (Box 34)
    See Heydner, Rolf
  - Gramm, Hanns (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 26; 12p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - (enc: Gramm, H. to Brüser, E. Jan. 30, 1929), 1929 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - H. Gramm -- to E. Brüser, 1929 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Gramm, H., Jan. 30, 1929)
    - H. Gramm -- to Otto E. Reimer, 1928 Jan. 13; 1p.
  - Grammer, Jacob (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 11; 1p.
  - Granger, L.D. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 11; 1p.
  - Grangvist, Hilma (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 21
  - Grant, C.B. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 2p.
  - Grant, E.J. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 20; 1p.
  - Grant, Frances R. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 21; 1p.
  - Grant, J.C. Boileau (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 June 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 June 16; 1p.
  - Gratacap, L.T. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To James Terry?, 1887 June 15
  - Graubart, E. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 6
  - Graue, Erwin (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p.
    - ToBoas, 1936 May 15; 1p.
  - Grautoff, Walter (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1918 Aug. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 May 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 July 7; 1p.
    - (Enc: Copy of letter from H. Alexander to Hon. Felix Frankfurter, July 6, 1918), 1918 July 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 July 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr.; 1p.
  - Graves, G.E. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1914 July 25; 2p.
  - Graves, Louis (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1914 May 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 12
  - Graves, Mortimer (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 May 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 June 5; 1p.
    - (Enc: International school of American archaeology and ethnology. List of publications), 1939 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 June 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 May 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 22; 1p.
    - (Enc: Prentice, Wm. Kelly to American Council of Learned Societies. Comm. on Native Amer. Languages), 1941 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - M. Graves -- to J.H. Finley
      - See Finley, J.H., Dec. 29, 1921
    - M. Graves -- from F.D. Lessing, 1939 Apr. 23
    - (Enc. with Lessing, F.D., Apr. 23, 1939)
  - Graves, William W. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 4; 3p.
    - (Enc: Graves, W.W. to A. Hrdlicka Graves, W.W. to Hl Westergaard Westergaard, H. to Graves, W.W., Oct. 7, 1919 Sept. 9, 1919 Oct. 14, 1919)
    - Graves, W.W. -- An appeal for human embryological material, 1920 Mar. 29; 2p.
    - W.W. Graves -- to A. Hrdlicka, 1919 Oct. 7; 3p.
    - (Enc: originally with Graves, W.W., Dec. 4, 1919)
    - W.W. Graves -- from H. Westergaard, 1919 Oct. 14; 1p.
  - Gray, G.M.W. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 9; 2p.
  - Gray, H.A. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p.
  - Gray, Howard A. -- (cont'd.) (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - (Enc: Anthropological society urges film libraries. Educational screen, March, 1935), 1935 Apr. 24; 1p.
  - Gray, Louis H. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - L.H. Gray -- from B. Laufer, 1905 Jan. 25
    - L.H. Gray -- from B. Laufer, 1905 Feb. 8
  - Grayson, F.W. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1917 May 8
  - Grayzel, Solomon (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1940 June 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 July 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 June 7; 1p.
  - University of Graz (Box 34)
    - FB -- to Rector, 1927 Apr. 5; 1p.
      See Paul, Hans - Bibliothek, Tech. Hochsch.
      See Speyer, James - Bibliothek, Tech. Hochsch.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 5; 1p.
  - Grazzi, E. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1928 June 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 15; 1p.
  - Great Britain. Ambassador (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 June 25; 1p.
    - From George Marshall, 1940 Feb. 29
    - (Enc: with Marshall, Mar. 13, 1940), 1940 Mar. 13
  - Great Britain. Legation (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 20; 1p.
  - Great Britain. Undersecretary of State for the Colonies (Box 34)
    - From P. Kirchhoff, 1932 Jan. 28
    - To P. Kirchhoff, 1932 Feb. 15; 2p.
  - Greely, A.W. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 18; 1p.
  - Green, Martin (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1892 Aug. 10; 1p.
  - Greenberg, Joseph H. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 24; 1p.
  - Greene, Betty (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 3; 1p.
  - Greene, Jerome D. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 23; 1p.
  - Greene, T.M. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 17; 1p.
      (Enc: Boas, F. Comments on "Liberal Education and Democracy")
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 5; 1p.
  - Greenleaf, W.E. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 28; 1p.
  - Greenman, Milton J. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - M.J. Greenman -- from Franz Keibel, 1920 Nov. 22
  - Greenshield, E.W.T. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 9; 4p.
  - Greenway, Cornelius (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1936 July 16; 2p.
  - Greenwich House (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1930 June 3; 1p.
  - Greet, Cabell (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 11; 1p.
  - Greet, William C. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1930 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 8; 1p.
  - Gregg, Alan (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 30; 1p.
  - Gregg, J.E. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1925 June 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 June 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 28; 1p.
  - Gregg, Richard B. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 23p.
    - (Attached to: Gregg, Richard B., June 18,1926)
    - R.B. Gregg -- to Mrs. Stokes, 1926 June 18; 5p.
      (Attached: Notes on miscegenation by R.B. Gregg)
  - Gregory, E.H. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 29
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 15
  - Gregory, Herbert Ernest (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 31; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 July 23; 1p.
    - (Enc: Hornbostel, E. von, July 1929)
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - H.E. Gregory -- from Karl von den Steinen, 1921 Dec. 14; 2p.
  - Gregory, Louise (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 21; 1p.
  - Gregory, Richard (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 13; 1p.
  - Gregory, T.W. (Box 34)
    - T.W. Gregory -- to J.M. Cattell, 1918 July 8; 1p.
  - Gregory, William K. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 July 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 July 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 9; 2p.
    - (Enc: Frick, C. to Gregory, W.K. Apr.8,1930), 1931 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - (Attached: card of Moorehouse, G.W.), 1931 Feb. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - (Enc: Gregory, W.K. to Watson, E.C. Feb. 28, 1931), 1931 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 7; 1p.
    - (Enc: Gregory, W.K to Danforth, C.H. July 8, 1931, 1931 July 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 28; 1p.
    - W.K. Gregory -- from C.H. Danforth, 1931 June 29
    - (Enc. with Danforth, C.H., June 29, 1931)
    - W.K. Gregory -- to C.H. Danforth, 1931 July 8; 1p.
    - W.K. Gregory -- from C. Frick, 1930 Apr. 8
    - (Enc. with Gregory, W.K., Apr. 9, 1930)
    - W.K. Gregory -- to E.C. Watson, 1931 Feb. 28; 1p.
  - Greiner, Dorothy (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 6; 1p.
  - Grendon, Felix (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1909 June 25
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec.; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec.; 2p.
    - F. Grendon -- to Miss Andrews, 1909 June 29
  - Greulich, W.W. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1941 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 20; 1p.
  - Greutzfeld (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Kallmann, Franz, Oct. 26, 1936)
  - Grey, Robert G. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1931 June 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 17; 1p.
    - (Enc: Bruckner Society of America), 1931 Dec. 14; 7p.
  - Griebsch, Max (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 24; 2p.
  - Griffin, A.J. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 6; 2p.
  - Griffin, James O. (Box 34)
    - J.O. Griffin -- from A.L. Kroeber, 1905 Oct. 31
    - (See Kroeber, A.L., Nov. 1, 1905)
  - Griffin, William (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 7
  - Griffis, Mrs. Elliott (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 1; 1p.
  - Griffith, John (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 10; 3p.
  - Griggs, R. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 28; 1p.
  - Grigorien, A. (?) (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1908 Aug. 27; 2p.
  - Grinnell, George Bird (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1892 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 June 27
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 10; 1p.
  - Groot, J.J.M. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6
  - Grope, Ernst (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1895 Oct. 1; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Aug. 4; 4p.
  - Grosqueaeen(?) M.P.E. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 6
  - Gross, Albert H. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 28; 1p.
  - Gross, Bella (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 25; 1p.
  - Gross, Rev. Francis (Box 34)
    - See R, G.P., Sept. 20, 1933
  - Gross, G.J. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 13
  - Grossgebauer, John (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p.
  - Grossman, B.A. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 15; 1p.
  - Grossmann, Maximilian (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1891 Oct. 24; 1p.
  - Grosvenor, Gilbert H. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 18; 1p.
  - Grosz, G. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 14; 1p.
  - Groszmann, M.P.E. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 30
  - Grotewahl, Max (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 7; 1p.
  - Group for Amer. Indian linguistics. Administrative committee (Box 34)
    - From Kent, R.G., May 20, 1938
  - Groves, H.M. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1934 May 29; 1p.
  - Growfreed, Inc. (Box 34)
    See Grautoff, Walter
  - Grube, Lilly (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 11
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 29; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Sept. 14; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 25; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 3; 4p.
  - Grube, Wilhelm (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 10; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 7; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Apr. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 July 2
  - Gruenberg, B.C. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 12; 1p.
  - Gruener, G. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - G.Gruener -- from P.V.C. Bauer, 1922; 1p.
  - Gruening, E.H. (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1924 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 June 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 28; 1p.
  - Grünwedel, Albert (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1886 July 25
    - To Boas, 1886 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1887 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1887 May 6
    - To Boas, 1887 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 16; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 6; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 5; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Aug. 20; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Sept. 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 12; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1890 Jan. 15; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1890 May 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1890 (end); 4p.
    - To Boas, n.d.; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1891 May 20; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1891 Sept. 5; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1892 Mar.; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1892 May 13; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1896 July 17
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1910 July 18
    - To Boas, 1910 July 18
  - Gruepe (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 14; (postcard)
  - Gruldi(?), Ennero (Box 34)
    - E. Gruldi -- to D. Efrón, 1939 Mar. 27; 1p.
  - Grunebaum, G.E. von (Box 34)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 27; 1p.
  - Grunwald, Werner (Box 34)
    - W. Grunwald -- from T.F. Murphy, 1941 Dec. 31
  - Gruschivity, L. (Box 34)
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 16
  - Grusd, Edward E. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 8; 1p.